Her quest to expose the truth takes her to the verge of no return
Òlòtūré is a drama, crime film directed by Kenneth Gyang.
In Lagos, Nigeria, young, naive Nigerian journalist Òlòtūré goes
undercover to expose the shady underworld of human trafficking.
Unused to this brutal environment, crawling with ruthless traders and pimps, Òlòtūré finds warmth
and friendship with Blessing, Linda and Beauty, the prostitutes she lives with.
However, she gets drawn into their lifestyle and finds it difficult to cope.
In her quest to uncover the truth, she pays the ultimate price -
one that takes her to the verge of no return.
Oloture, played by Sharon Ooja.
Emeka, played by Blossom Chukwujekwu.
Alero, played by Omoni Oboli.
Linda, played by Omowunmi Dada.
Beauty, played by Bukola Oladipupo.
Blessing, played by Kemi Lala Akindoju.
Òlòtūré is a 2019 Nigerian crime drama film directed by Kenneth Gyang
from a screenplay by Yinka Ogun and Craig Freimond.
It stars Sharon Ooja, Beverly Osu, Ada Ameh and Blossom Chukwujekwu.
The tone is dark and emotional.